Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 22.1C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 22.0C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 22.2C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 22.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 22.1C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 22.0C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.8C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.7C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.6C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.5C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.4C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.2C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.1C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 21.0C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.9C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.8C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.7C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.6C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.5C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.4C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.2C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.1C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 20.0C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.9C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.8C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.7C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.6C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.5C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.4C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.2C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.1C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.0C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.2C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 19.3C
Depth: 0.1m | Temp: 19.2C
Depth: 0.3m | Temp: 19.2C
Depth: 0.3m | Temp: 19.1C
Depth: 0.4m | Temp: 19.1C
Depth: 0.5m | Temp: 19.1C
Depth: 0.7m | Temp: 19.0C
Depth: 0.8m | Temp: 18.9C
Depth: 0.7m | Temp: 18.8C
Depth: 0.8m | Temp: 18.8C
Depth: 0.9m | Temp: 18.8C
Depth: 1.0m | Temp: 18.7C
Depth: 1.1m | Temp: 18.7C
Depth: 1.0m | Temp: 18.6C
Depth: 0.9m | Temp: 18.6C
Depth: 1.1m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 0.9m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 0.8m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 1.0m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 1.1m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 1.0m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.9m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.8m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.7m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.9m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.9m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 1.0m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 1.1m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 1.2m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 1.3m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 1.4m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 1.4m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 1.5m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 1.6m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 1.7m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 1.8m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 1.9m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 2.1m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 2.3m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 2.4m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 2.5m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 2.6m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 2.7m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 2.8m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 2.9m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.0m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.1m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.2m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.3m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.4m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.5m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.6m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 3.9m | Temp: 18.0C
Depth: 4.0m | Temp: 18.0C
Depth: 4.2m | Temp: 18.0C
Depth: 4.3m | Temp: 18.0C
Depth: 4.2m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 4.3m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 4.4m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 4.5m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 4.6m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 4.7m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 4.7m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 4.8m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 4.9m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 5.0m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 5.1m | Temp: 17.7C
Depth: 5.2m | Temp: 17.7C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.7C
Depth: 5.4m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 5.5m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.2m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.3m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.4m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.5m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.6m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.5m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.6m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.6m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.5C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 16.4C
Depth: 10.5m | Temp: 16.4C
Depth: 10.6m | Temp: 16.3C
Depth: 10.5m | Temp: 16.2C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 16.2C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.1C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.0C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.5m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.6m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 16.0C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 16.0C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 16.0C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 16.1C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 16.2C
Depth: 9.2m | Temp: 16.2C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 16.3C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 16.3C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 16.4C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 16.5C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.2m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.6m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.6m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 16.5C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 16.5C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 16.4C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 16.3C
Depth: 11.0m | Temp: 16.2C
Depth: 11.0m | Temp: 16.1C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 16.1C
Depth: 11.0m | Temp: 16.0C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 15.8C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 15.7C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 15.6C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 15.5C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 15.4C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 15.2C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 15.1C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 14.9C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 14.8C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 14.6C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 14.5C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 14.4C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 14.4C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 14.3C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 14.2C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 14.1C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 14.0C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 13.9C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 13.8C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 13.7C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 13.6C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 13.5C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 13.4C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 13.3C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 13.2C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 13.2C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 13.1C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 13.0C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 12.9C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 12.9C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 12.8C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 12.7C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 12.7C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 12.7C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 12.6C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 12.6C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 12.5C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 12.4C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 12.3C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 12.2C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 12.1C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 12.0C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 11.8C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 11.7C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.7C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.6C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.5C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.4C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 11.3C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 10.8C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 10.7C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 10.6C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.5C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 10.4C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 10.4C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 12.5m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 10.2C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 10.2C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 9.9C
Depth: 12.5m | Temp: 9.9C
Depth: 12.7m | Temp: 9.9C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 9.9C
Depth: 12.8m | Temp: 9.8C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 9.8C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 9.8C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 9.7C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 9.6C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 9.5C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 9.4C
Depth: 13.1m | Temp: 9.3C
Depth: 13.2m | Temp: 9.3C
Depth: 13.2m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 13.3m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 13.4m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 13.4m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 13.5m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 13.6m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 13.7m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 13.8m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 13.9m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 14.1m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 14.1m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 14.2m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 14.3m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 14.4m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 14.6m | Temp: 8.7C
Depth: 14.7m | Temp: 8.7C
Depth: 14.8m | Temp: 8.6C
Depth: 14.9m | Temp: 8.6C
Depth: 15.0m | Temp: 8.6C
Depth: 15.1m | Temp: 8.5C
Depth: 15.2m | Temp: 8.5C
Depth: 15.3m | Temp: 8.4C
Depth: 15.4m | Temp: 8.4C
Depth: 15.5m | Temp: 8.3C
Depth: 15.6m | Temp: 8.3C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 8.2C
Depth: 15.8m | Temp: 8.2C
Depth: 15.8m | Temp: 8.1C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 8.1C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 8.0C
Depth: 15.8m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 7.8C
Depth: 15.6m | Temp: 7.8C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 7.7C
Depth: 15.6m | Temp: 7.7C
Depth: 15.6m | Temp: 7.6C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 7.6C
Depth: 15.6m | Temp: 7.5C
Depth: 15.5m | Temp: 7.5C
Depth: 15.7m | Temp: 7.5C
Depth: 15.8m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 15.8m | Temp: 7.5C
Depth: 15.9m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 16.0m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 16.1m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 16.0m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.3C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 16.1m | Temp: 7.3C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.3C
Depth: 16.1m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 16.3m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 16.4m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 16.5m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 16.3m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 16.4m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 16.5m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 16.6m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 16.7m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 16.8m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 16.9m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 17.1m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 17.2m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 17.2m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 17.1m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 17.1m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 17.0m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 17.0m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.9m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.8m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.7m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.6m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.5m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.4m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.3m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.5m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.4m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.3m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.5m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.6m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.7m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.8m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.6m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.5m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.4m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.3m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 16.1m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 6.9C
Depth: 16.2m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 16.3m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 16.0m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 15.9m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 15.8m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 15.6m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 15.5m | Temp: 7.0C
Depth: 15.6m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 15.5m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 15.4m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 15.3m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 15.1m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 15.0m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 14.9m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 14.8m | Temp: 7.1C
Depth: 14.8m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 14.7m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 14.6m | Temp: 7.2C
Depth: 14.7m | Temp: 7.3C
Depth: 14.8m | Temp: 7.3C
Depth: 14.4m | Temp: 7.3C
Depth: 14.2m | Temp: 7.4C
Depth: 14.3m | Temp: 7.5C
Depth: 14.2m | Temp: 7.5C
Depth: 14.1m | Temp: 7.5C
Depth: 14.1m | Temp: 7.6C
Depth: 13.9m | Temp: 7.6C
Depth: 14.2m | Temp: 7.7C
Depth: 14.1m | Temp: 7.7C
Depth: 14.2m | Temp: 7.8C
Depth: 14.1m | Temp: 7.8C
Depth: 14.3m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 14.4m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 14.6m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 14.7m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 14.4m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 14.3m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 14.2m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 14.1m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 13.9m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 13.8m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 13.7m | Temp: 7.9C
Depth: 13.7m | Temp: 8.0C
Depth: 13.5m | Temp: 8.0C
Depth: 13.4m | Temp: 8.0C
Depth: 13.3m | Temp: 8.0C
Depth: 13.2m | Temp: 8.0C
Depth: 13.2m | Temp: 8.1C
Depth: 13.1m | Temp: 8.1C
Depth: 13.1m | Temp: 8.2C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 8.2C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 8.2C
Depth: 12.8m | Temp: 8.2C
Depth: 12.8m | Temp: 8.3C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 8.3C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 8.4C
Depth: 12.7m | Temp: 8.4C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 8.4C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 8.5C
Depth: 12.5m | Temp: 8.5C
Depth: 12.5m | Temp: 8.6C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 8.6C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 8.6C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 8.7C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 8.7C
Depth: 12.7m | Temp: 8.7C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.5m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 12.5m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 12.6m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 12.7m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 12.8m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 12.7m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 12.9m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 13.1m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 13.2m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 13.1m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 13.2m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 13.3m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 13.2m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 13.0m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.8m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.7m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.5m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 8.8C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 8.9C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 9.0C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 9.1C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 9.2C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 9.3C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 9.4C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 9.6C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 9.7C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 9.8C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 10.2C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 10.4C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 10.5C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 10.6C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 10.7C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 10.8C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 11.3C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 11.4C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 11.5C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 11.6C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 11.7C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 11.8C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 11.8C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 11.8C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.7C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 11.6C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 11.5C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 11.4C
Depth: 12.4m | Temp: 11.3C
Depth: 12.3m | Temp: 11.3C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.8C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.7C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.6C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.5C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.5C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.4C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.4C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 10.2C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.2C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.2C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 12.1m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 12.2m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 9.9C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 9.9C
Depth: 11.9m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 12.0m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 10.0C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 10.1C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 10.2C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 10.3C
Depth: 11.8m | Temp: 10.4C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 10.4C
Depth: 11.7m | Temp: 10.5C
Depth: 11.6m | Temp: 10.5C
Depth: 11.5m | Temp: 10.6C
Depth: 11.4m | Temp: 10.6C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 10.7C
Depth: 11.3m | Temp: 10.8C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 10.9C
Depth: 11.2m | Temp: 11.0C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.0m | Temp: 11.1C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.2C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.3C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.4C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.5C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.6C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.7C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.8C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 11.9C
Depth: 11.1m | Temp: 12.0C
Depth: 11.0m | Temp: 12.1C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 12.2C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 12.2C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 12.3C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 12.4C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 12.5C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 12.6C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 12.8C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 12.9C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 13.0C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 13.1C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 13.3C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 13.4C
Depth: 10.9m | Temp: 13.5C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 13.6C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 13.7C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 13.8C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 13.9C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 14.0C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 14.0C
Depth: 10.8m | Temp: 14.1C
Depth: 10.7m | Temp: 14.2C
Depth: 10.5m | Temp: 14.3C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 14.4C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 14.5C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 14.6C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 14.7C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 14.7C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 14.8C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 14.9C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 15.0C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 15.1C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 15.2C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 15.3C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 15.4C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 15.5C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 15.6C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 15.7C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 15.8C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 15.9C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.0C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.2C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.2C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 16.3C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 16.3C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 16.4C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 16.4C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 16.5C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.5C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.5C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.6C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.7C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.2m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.4m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.2m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.1m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.4m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 5.5m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.5m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.2m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.3m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.5m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 6.5m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.0m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.5m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.4m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.3m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.8C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.2m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.1m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 10.0m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.8m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.7m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.6m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.5m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 9.4m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.3m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 9.1m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.9m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.7m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.5m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.4m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.3m | Temp: 16.9C
Depth: 8.1m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 8.2m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.9m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.7m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.5m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.6m | Temp: 17.0C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.2m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.3m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.1m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 7.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 6.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 6.9m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 6.7m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 6.6m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 6.4m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 6.2m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.1C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.4m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.1m | Temp: 17.2C
Depth: 5.2m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.4m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.5m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 6.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.6m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.5m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.3m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.2m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.1m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 4.9m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 5.0m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 4.8m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 4.7m | Temp: 17.3C
Depth: 4.6m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 4.5m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 4.4m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 4.2m | Temp: 17.4C
Depth: 4.1m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 4.0m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 3.9m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 3.7m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 3.6m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 3.4m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 3.2m | Temp: 17.5C
Depth: 3.1m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 3.0m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 2.8m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 2.6m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 2.5m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 2.8m | Temp: 17.6C
Depth: 2.8m | Temp: 17.7C
Depth: 3.0m | Temp: 17.7C
Depth: 3.1m | Temp: 17.7C
Depth: 3.3m | Temp: 17.7C
Depth: 3.4m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.5m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.6m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.7m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.4m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.2m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.1m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.0m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.2m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.1m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.0m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 2.9m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 3.1m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 2.8m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 2.9m | Temp: 17.8C
Depth: 2.6m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 2.8m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 2.4m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 1.9m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 1.8m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 1.6m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 1.4m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 0.9m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 0.5m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 0.4m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 17.9C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.0C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.1C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.6C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.7C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 0.4m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.2m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.4m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.3m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 0.1m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.2C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.3C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.4C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.5C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.6C
Depth: 0.0m | Temp: 18.7C